politicalPoll = [
    voterDemographic = [ 
        {
            question: "What is your political affiliation?",
            answers: [ "Democrat", "Green Party", "Independant", "Libertarian", "Other", "Republican", "Unaffiliated"]
        },
        {
            question: "Have you been a member of the same political party your entire voting career?",
            answers: [ "Yes", "No", "Changed once", "Changed twice", "Changed more than 3 times"]
        },
        {
            question: "Do you vote in national elections?",
            answers: ["Always", "Never", "More than half the time", "Half the time", "Less than half the time"]
        },
        {
            question: "Do you vote in local elections",
            answers: ["Always", "Never", "More than half the time", "Half the time", "Less than half the time"]
        },
        {
            question: "How likely are you to vote in upcoming elections?",
            answers: ["Very Likely", "Somewhat Likely", "I dont know", "Somewhate Unlikely", "Very Unlikely"]
        },
        {
            question: "How many national elections have you voted in?",
            answers: ["none", "1-5", "5-10", "10-15", "15-20", "20+"]
        },
        {
            question: "Do you always vote for candidates in your political party?",
            answer: ["Always", "Never", "More than half the time", "Half the time", "Less than half the time"]
        },
        {
            question: "Do you believe that political polls are fairly accurate?",
            answer: ["Always", "Never", "More than half the time", "Half the time", "Less than half the time"]
        }  
    ],
    currentLeadership = [
        {
            question: "How would you rate the president on their ability to effectively fill their roll? 10 being perfectly effective and 1 being completely ineffective.",
            answers: ["10", "9", "8", "7", "6", "5", "4", "3", "2", "1"]
        },
        {
            question: "How would you rate the Electoral College on their ability to effectively fill their roll? 10 being perfectly effective and 1 being completely ineffective.",
            answers: ["10", "9", "8", "7", "6", "5", "4", "3", "2", "1"]
        },
        {
            question: "Do you GENERALLY trust elected political figures?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No", "Only Members in my affiliated party"]
        },
        {
            question: "GENERALLY How confident are you in the ability of world leaders to address the worldâ€™s biggest challenges?",
            answer: ["Very Confident", "Somewhat Confident", "I don't know", "Less Confident", "Not confident at all"]
        }
    ],
    currentSystem = [
        {
            question: "Do you believe in the impeachment process in the United States?",
            answer: ["Yes", "No", "I don't know", "Sometimes"]
        },
        {
            question: "Are you in favor of or against mail-in voting?",
            answer: ["Completely in favor", "Somewhat in favor", "I don't know", "I don't care", "Somewhat against", "Completely Against"]
        }
    ],
    economics = [
        {
            question: "Thinking about the job situation in America today, would you say that it is a good time to find a quality job?",
            answers: ["Very good time", "Somewhat good time", "I don't know", "Somewhat not a good time", "Not a good time"]
        },
        {
            question: "How would you rate economic conditions in this country, 10 = great 1 = poor?",
            answers: ["10", "9", "8", "7", "6","5","4","3","2","1"]
        }

    ],
    forgeignPolicy = [
        {
            question: "Do you think it best for the future of our country if we take an active part in world affairs or if we stay uninvolved?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No", "Sometimes"]
        }
    ]
    // defense = [

    // ],
    // climate = [

    // ],
    // healthCare = [

    // ],
    // civilRights = [

    // ],

]